========ED=======
我看看
You ruffians do know that I'm Kongou Mitsuko of Tokiwadai, right?
貴方方　私を 常盤台の婚後光子と知っての狼藉ですの
狼藉
Ruffians?
さすがお嬢様は 俺達と違うお言葉をお使いだ なあ
I guess it's to be expected of an ojousama.
She's using really eloquent words, isn't she?
どうやら日本語が通じない方なようね
It seems that you don't understand Japanese, do you?
ならば　お相手致しましょう
Well, how about this: I'll be your opponent!
どうした　頭が痛いのか
What's wrong? Does your head hurt?
これは
This is...
誰だテメィ
Who the hell are you?
おいおい　女の子にちょっかい出すってのは
Hey hey, messing with a girl is something...
いただけねえなあ
I just can't accept.
だ　れ
Wh-Who...?
After something like this,
<skill out>
このところ頻発していた武装無能力集団による能力者狩りも
the recent series of ability user hunts done by Skill-Out...
どうやらこれで打ち止めですわね
should finally come to an end.
平気ですか
-Are you all right?
ええい
Yes...
It was rather unexpected of them to target Kongou Mitsuko, however.
まさか婚後光子を狙うとは
どれだけととうをくもうとも
No matter how many there are, there's no way these stray Level 0's could ever beat a Level 4 ability user.
<level 0>　　　　　　　　　　　<level 4>
無能力者のはぐれ者たちが大能力者の能力者に敵うはずがないと
この連中も骨身に沁みて
These bunch should have understood thi—
That doesn't seem to be the case here.
それが違うらしいの
彼女の話では　自分が何故かうまく能力が使えなかった
According to her story, for some reason she wasn't able to use her powers and then a mysterious guy appeared...
そこに謎な人物が現れて
Tamezou?
為蔵
固法先輩
Konori-sempai?
Ah, sorry. I wonder if Uiharu's questioning is going well.
おう　ごめん　えっと　初春さんの聞き取り上手く行ってるかな
Yes.
ええ　それから私　気を失なってしまって
After that, I lost consciousness.
気がついたら全員倒されていた
And when you came to, everyone was defeated?
ええ
Yes.
何が覚えっていることがあったら
Is there anything else you can remember?
そうですね
Let's see... How should I say this?
なんと申しましょうか
あの革でできた　自動二輪車に乗る殿方がよく着てらっしゃる
That leather-made...
The thing that men riding those two wheel vehicles often wear...
革ジャン
A leather jacket?
そう　それですわ
Yes! That's it!
黒い 革ジャン
A black leather jacket!
それとそれを持った殿方の背中に黒い大きいな蜘蛛の刺青を見たような
And I think I saw what looked like a
tattoo of a big black spider on his back.
固法先輩
Konori-sempai? Is something the matter? I've been wondering for a while...
どうかなさいまして
先ほどから何だか
No, it's nothing at all.
何でもない
So, the guy with the leather jacket and the tattoo of a black spider must be the one who did these guys in?
その革ジャンに黒蜘蛛刺青の男が
こいつらを遣っ付けたんでしょうかね
響き合う願いが今覚醒めてく
脑海中回响着的愿望现已苏醒
譲れない未来のために
为了绝不可相让的未来
巡り逢う運命を超えたその先に
只因在超越命运的前方
この想い輝くから
这份思念正闪耀着光芒
ここじゃない未来に
在那并非归属的未来
想い託してみては
寄存着这份思念
強さの本当の意味を
继续寻找着那
搜し続けてた
强大的真正意义
ありのままの痛みを
将各种痛苦
受け入れるその意味を
全部承受的意义
明日へ走り続ける君に知った
是奔向明天的你告诉了我
巡りゆく景色が今流れてく
那眼前的景色现已过去
手繰り寄せた世界の先
那紧牵着双手的世界的前方
降り注ぐシグナルを躰で感じて
身体已感觉到其中所倾注的信号
解き放つ今全てを
此刻解放所有一切
Just truth in my heart
いつだって迷わないよ
无论何时都不应迷茫
消せない想いがあるから
因为有着无法磨灭的思念
解き明かす真実から瞳を逸らさずに
直视那已经揭开的真相
I'll reach the next stage to realize all.
確かな絆信じて
请相信这份羁绊
<Big spider>
大蜘蛛
"Big Spider" ?
それが一連の能力者狩りを行っていた組織の名前なんですか
Is that the name of the organization behind
the ones who are serial hunting ability users?
<Big spider>　　<skill out>
大蜘蛛は　武装無能力集団の中でもちょっとは名の知れた組織なの
Big Spider is an organization that is famous among Skill-Out.
かつてはそれなりにのプライドを持って
They used to have pride and actually understood right from wrong,
いっせいはわきまえてたんけど
最近は単なる無法者の集団になってしまた
but lately they've resorted to just being rogues.
The pride of a Skill-Out you say? In the end they're just a mob of people with inferiority complexes.
<skill out>
武装無能力集団のプライドと言われても
所詮は用すね悲願だ烏合の衆
Indeed. But inside, there is a smoking discontent, resentment, and un-erasable admiration for those with abilities...
そうね
でも　彼らの中にくすべる不満　憤り
それでも消せない能力者への憧れ
固法先輩　詳しいんですね
Konori-sempai, you're quite knowledgeable about this.
Well, yeah.
ま　まあねぇ
さすが先輩
Just what I expected from a sempai!
婚後さんが襲われた
Kongou-san was attacked?!
Now, now. Calm down, Onee-sama.
まあ　まあ　御姉様　落ち着いて
大勢で女の子襲うとか
Attacking a girl with numbers, those guys are scum!
男として最低じゃない
御坂さん　なんだか偉くテンション高いですね
Misaka-san, you're really worked up about this.
No, I just can't forgive those who don't do what they can and run from reality.
いや　私はただ　自分にできることやろうともしないで
現実から逃げてるだけなやつか許せないっていうか
Ehhh... It seems like you're talking about me.
なんか自分の事言われてるみたい
Eh? Saten-san, you're different.
佐天さんは違うよ
Yeah. crossing the street in a group while the light is red is how the Skill-Outs seem to operate.
そうですわ
赤信号　皆で渡ればなのが武装無能力集団
一人で渡る切った佐天さんとは　きもの座り方が根本的に
But Saten-san, you managed cross it all by yourself! You're much more courageous than they are.
Shirai-san, it doesn't seem like you're defending her at all..
白井さん　全然フォローになってない気が
<skill out>
でも武装無能力集団っていいや
But it seems like Skill-Outs are just jealous and angry Level 0's.
<level 0>
やさぐれ無能力者でしょう
それがどうして能力者狩りなんか
What are they trying to accomplish
by hunting down people with power?
多勢に無勢　いかに優秀な能力者と言えと
Even if you have a number and are skilled, it's
tough to take on that many people by yourself.
大勢の人間を相手にする事は難しいんですの
On top of that, we have information that the organization
Big Spider has acquired illegal weapons on the black market.
<Big spider>
それに　大蜘蛛という組織は
闇ルートから非合法な武器を手に入れているという情報もあります
Hmm, I wonder if those guys would give me some action?
そいつら　いっそう私に絡んで来てくれないかな
御姉様
Onee-sama...
If you want some action, I'll always give you some—
絡んでほしいなら　黒子がいつでも絡みますの
That's not what I meant!
そうじゃなくて
出てけ
だったら私を付き合ってください
で　結局その婚後さん襲った武装無能力集団の連中で
In the end, everyone from that group who attacked Kongou-san was caught, right?
皆　捕まったんだよね
It seems those guys were all defeated in one blow by a stranger.
謎な人物が一撃で倒したそうです
Wow an ally of justice who was passing by, huh?
通りすがりの正義の味方
とんでもない
Not at all!
If they're using force and are not a part of Anti-Skills or Judgement, then they're just ordinary, idiotic criminals!
警備員でも风纪委员でもないのに
力を行使するなんて言語道断的として犯罪者ですわ
まさか　先輩なんですか
Is it really you, sempai...?
黒妻さん
Kurozuma-san!
それが　為蔵さんたちをやったのは
About that guy who got Tamezou-san's group...
出鱈目を言うんじゃねえよ
Don't give me that shit!
I just...
俺を確か
そうだ　あいつは死んだ
That's right, he's dead.
あれで生きているはずはねえだ
There's no way he could still be alive.
おい　お前ら
Hey you guys! What's my name?!
おれの名前は
黒妻綿流
Kurozuma Wataru!
そうだ　俺は黒妻
That's right, I'm Kurozuma.
<Big spider>
大蜘蛛の頭だ
The boss of Big Spider!
お前らは忘れたわけじゃねえだろな
You guys haven't forgotten that, right?
能力者達が俺達を見るあの目を
Guys with power that look at us with those eyes! Those eyes!
あの馬鹿にしきた目を
Those guys look at us like we were idiots!
That's why we beat them up!
だから　俺達はあいつらをぶっ飛ばす
本気を出した武装無能力集団の恐ろしさを見せてやれ
I'll show them what happens when Skill-Out gets serious!
オース
また大蜘蛛が
Big Spider again?
今週だけでもう三件目
Already 3 victims just this week...
連中ピッチを上げて来てますわ
They seemed to have upped the rate.
やっぱここは一発ドカンと
I should give those guys a hit.
御姉様
Onee-sama.
御姉様のドカンは被害が大きくなりすぎますの
Your methods cause way too many victims.
大蜘蛛が勢力を伸ばすて来たのは　二年ぐらい前からみたいですね
Big Spider seems to have expanded its influence about two years ago.
武器を手にして犯罪行為繰り返すようになったのも　ちょうどその頃
It's also about the time that they acquired weapons and started committing crimes.
なるほど　武器を手に入れ調子付いてたでわけね
I see. They got some weapons and now they think they're all high and mighty.
でも　そんな物　学園都市の外からどうやって持ち込むんだろう
But how did they get those in from outside Academy City?
物資の流通は厳重に管理されてるし
The flow of goods is strictly supervised,
非合法な物なんて　当然シャットアウトされてるはずじゃない
so illegal goods should be shut out, right?
蛇の道は蛇と言いますから
They say that only those in the trade know those routes...
連中にその道を作った上げたやつが　他にいるのかもね
Is there anyone else who could have possibly opened that path?
バックがいると
You mean an inside job?
Yeah.
なるほど　調べてみる価値がありそうですの
I'll see. It's worth looking into.
あの　それからもう一つ
Um, there's one more thing, I found out who Big Spider's leader is.
大蜘蛛のリーダーが分りました
名前は黒妻綿流　かなりあくどい男のようです
His name is Kurozuma Wataru.
He seems like a pretty big criminal.
仲間も平気で裏切るようなやつらしいですね
He doesn't seem to care a bit about betraying his comrades.
グループから脱げるなんていようものなら
It's said he'll even shoot you in the
back if you want to escape the group.
背中から打ちかねない男だと言われています
つまり　最低の男というわけですわね
In other words, he's the worst kind of scum isn't he?
Speaking of backs, it seems that he has a tattoo of a spider on his back.
背中と言えば　その人背中に蜘蛛の刺青入れてるらしいですよ
A spider?
蜘蛛の
あれ　婚後さんを助けたと言う男にも
Oh? There was one on the back of Kongou's savior, too.
その男が黒妻綿流
That man was Kurozuma Wataru? What could this mean?
どいうことですの
結局　助けたんじゃなくて　単なる仲間割れたとか
So, it wasn't that he saved her, but rather it was the result of an internal conflict.
He's the kind of guy who shoots people in the back, right?
背中から打ちかねないの男なんでしょう
I see. That's a possibility.
なるほど
その可能性はありますわね
えっと　彼らは第十学区の通称ストレンジと呼ばれる地域を根城にしています
Uh, they're using the Tenth Academic
District, a.k.a. "Strange", as their hide out.
行くの
Are you going?
管轄外ではありますけど
Though it's outside of our jurisdiction, if we say its an investigation from Section 7, then it's logical at least.
第七学区内で発生した事件の調査だと言えば筋は通りますの
固法先輩
Konori-sempai.
ごめん
I'm sorry, there's a report I have to wrap up by today.
私どうしても今日中に報告書をまとめなっきゃならんなくて
Eh? Then, shall we go?
じゃあ　行こうか
行くって　御姉様
Go— Onee-sama?!
固法先輩のピンチヒッターよ ほら
I'm filling in for Konori-sempai, now. Let's go!
Onee-sama! Oh, you're being so cruel to me!
御姉様
あれー　ご無体なぁ
白井さん
Shirai-san seems... happy.
嬉しそう
ここが
This is Big Spider's headquarters.
<Big spider>
大蜘蛛の根城
通称ストレンジですの
A.k.a. Strange.
Eh? Wonderful... not really.
素敵　とは　言いにくいわね
水清ければ魚は済ますと言いますけれど
They say if the water is too clear, fish won't live there.
それにしても
Despite that...
<skill out>
まあ　武装無能力集団をやってるような連中が住むには
Well, it could be a fitting place for those living as Skill-Out.
相応しいところなのかもね
Skill-Out are to blame,
武装無能力集団も武装無能力集団だけど
but to say things are under complete control while leaving sections like this, Academy City is also partially to blame.
完全管理って言いながら　こんな場所を放置してる学園都市も学園都市よね
何やらますます歓迎されている雰囲気ですの
It seems like it's becoming more of a welcoming environment
It's because you're wearing that.
あんたがそんなもの付けてるから
It's because you made me hurry, Onee-sama!
これは　御姉様が急かすから
私はちゃんと変装と
I was going to properly disguise...
Hey ladies, whatcha doing?
姉ちゃんたち　何してんの
Hey hey, Judgement?
おい　おい　风纪委员かよ
ほら　見なさい
こええ　これで捕まえちゃうのかなぁ
See, look what's happened.
I'm so scared, we might get arrested!
御姉様
Onee-sama.
何揉めてんのかなあ
What're you guys arguing about?
今更返さなえよ
You can't leave now that you've come this far.
待ちな
Hold it.
Making a pass at girls is...
女の子にちょっかい出すのは
いただけなえな
something I just can't respect.
はい？
Huh?
武装无能力集团
Skill Out
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Skill-Out
牛乳？
Milk?
Eh? What's your problem?
なんだ　テメィは
ちょっと待ってなぁ
Just wait for a minute.
え　っちょ
Huh? Um—
女の前だからって格好つけてんじゃねえぞ
There's no need to put up a front just because you're front of girls.
まあまあ　いいからテメィらはとっとと消えろう
Well, well...
Just get lost already, you bastard.
Umm, is this all right?
あの　こちらで宜しかったでしょか
Sorry for making you go all the way to get one.
あ　悪いなわざわざ
いいえ　じゃあ　俺らこの辺で
Well then, we'll be leaving!
Okay, take care.
おー　気いつけてなあ
やっぱ牛乳は武蔵野牛乳だなぁ
When it comes to milk it has to be Musashino milk!
助けてくれなんて言った覚えないけど
I don't remember asking for help.
そりゃ悪かった
Sorry about that.
昔の知り合いに君たちくらいの胸の女の子がいってさ
I had an old acquaintance that had a chest just like you girls.
ほっとけなかったんだ
I couldn't just leave you alone.
殿方に胸のことを言われたのに
Some stranger is talking about my chest...
不思議といやらしくない
For some strange reason, I don't feel defiled...
Hey, wait!
ちょっと待ちなさいよ
御姉様
Wait, Onee-sama!
あれ　美偉　もう帰ってんの
Oh, Mii. You're back already?
珍しいわね　こんなに早く
This is rare, you coming back this early.
风纪委员の仕事は
What about your Judgement work?
やってるはよちゃんと
I'm doing it properly.
あんたこそ偶には支部に顔を出しなさいよ
You should come show your face once in a while.
校内だけで十分よ
Working in the school is enough for me.
私は恋に青春に忙しいの
I'm busy with the love of my life.
たっく　あんたはいつもそうやって
Sheesh, you're always like that.
ねえ　何かあった
Hey, did something happen?
別に
Nothing.
そう
I see.
まあ　偶に早く帰って来たんだから
Since you're home early for once,
I'll leave dinner preparations to you.
今日の晩ご飯は美偉の番ね
ちょっと　碧美
Hey! Wait, Aomi!
へえ
Oh wow.
いいだろう　ちょっとした秘密な場所さ
Isn't it great? It's a little secret spot of mine.
下じゃ息が詰まるからなぁ
Since it gets a little stuffy down there.
ここは風が気持ちいいんだ
The breeze here feels great.
ここから見る　ストレンジ二年前と変わらねえな
The Strange I can see from here
hasn't changed in the past two years.
二年前
The past two years?
まあ　いろいろとなあ
A lot happened.
それにしても
Anyway, why are all the Skill-Outs concentrated here?
<skill out>
なぜ武装無能力集団の方々はこんな地区に集中して
あんた達には分らないさ
You guys wouldn't understand.
分らなくもないだよね
It's not like I don't understand.
何がですか
Understand what?
<skill out>
武装無能力集団の気持ち
The feelings of a Skill-Out.
やってもやってもレベルが上がらないとねぇ
No matter how hard you try, your level doesn't increase.
くじけそうになる時があるんだ
There are times where I feel hopeless, too.
なんかもう　何もかも投げ出しちゃおうかな　なんて
Like I just want to throw everything out.
何もかも投げ出ししまったんだよ　俺達は
We've thrown everything away.
We've ditched the "judging-everything-by-power" Academy City.
全てが能力で判断される学園都市を捨てたのさ
佐天さん
Saten-san.
I won't, I won't. I won't throw it all away any more.
ない　ない
私はもう投げ出したりしないよ
I promise I won't any more.
もう絶対　投げ出さない
俺達には　能力は手の届かない青空なのさ
To us, attaining power is like trying to reach to the sky.
この町の狭い路地から見上げるような　なぁ
Like seeing the sky from the narrow streets of this city.
でも　武装無能力集団は武装無能力集団でしょう
But Skill-Outs are Skill-Outs.
群れでやることは　ろくでもないことばっか
A group of idiots doing nothing but needless things.
Strict, aren't you?
手厳しいな
どころであんた達が何しに来たんだ
By the way, why are you guys here?
We're pursuing an organization called Big Spider.
<Big spider>
そうですの　私たち大蜘蛛という組織を追って
ここでその名前　あんまり出さないほうが賢明だぜ
I recommend not dropping that name around here.
でしたら　黒妻綿流という名前にここのあたりは
What do you know about a guy named Kurozuma Wataru, then?
知らないなあ
Never heard of him.
Well then, be careful on your way back.
ま　気いつけて帰りなよ
御姉様　どうしたんですの
Onee-sama, what's the matter?
なんかね　あの人気になるのよね
I'm a little curious about that guy.
What? What?! Onee-sama becoming interested in a guy?! I-I—
まあ　まああ　御姉様が殿方などに関心お持ちになるなんて黒子　黒子
痛い
Ow!
あの人　二年ぶりに帰って来たって言ってたでしょう
That guy said he returned here after being away for two years, right?
それがどうしたんですの
Yeah, what about it?
<big spider>
大蜘蛛が勢力を伸ばす始めたのも　二年前から
That's about the time that Big Spider expanded its influence.
何か引っかからない
Doesn't that seem a bit interesting?
言われてみれば
Now that you mention it...
他のところも当ってみよう
Let's go check elsewhere. We might find something.
何か分るかも知れない
Onee-sama, wait!
御姉様　待ってくださいですの
お前ら何やってんだ
What're you ass holes doing?!
能力者狩りの兵隊がもうこれで二重二重やられてんだぞう
We've lost twenty soldiers from the ability user hunts already!
On top of that, we've got no leads!
しかも手がかりなしだ
W-We are searching though...
さ　探してはいるんですが
探してるだ
Searching?! Don't just search! Find it!
探すんじゃねえだ
見つけるんだよ
何で見つからないか分るか
You understand why you can't find it, don't you?
俺達がなめられてるからだ
Because we've been put down!
いいか　野郎とも
All right you dumb asses, don't get put down!
なめられんじゃなえ
能力者を狩って
Hunt those ability users and show them
just how much power Big Spider really has!
<big spider>
俺達が大蜘蛛がどれほどの力を持ってるか　連中に教えてやるんだ
そうすれや俺達に逆らうやつなんぞういなくなるんだよ
Once we do that there won't be anyone who can resist us!
Roger!
はい
あいつが生きてる
That guy's alive.
いいえ　そんなはずがなえ
No, there's no way.
けど
But if he is...
もし　生きてったら
生きていったら
If he is...
なん　何だ
What're you guys? Skill-Outs?
<skill out>
お前らは武装無能力集団か
Ha ha! Tough luck for you guys.
相手が悪かったな　俺はレベル
I'm a Level—
どうだ　お前らもこんなにたくなかったら
How's that?! If you don't want anything else to happe—
よくもやってくれたな
You've really done it, now!
先までの威勢はどうした
What happened to that attitude you just had, hmm?
能力使ってみろよ
Try using your power now!
もっとも　殴られながら演算に集中できればな話だけどな
Well, that is, if you can concentrate while getting hit!
The rule of Academy City is survival of the fittest, right?
学園都市のルールは弱肉強食
今のお前らは食われる側だ
Now you guys are on the bottom of the food chain.
That means you guys are prepared to face defeat too, right?
じゃあ　あんた達も食われる覚悟があるってことね
We're Judgement!
<judgement>
风纪委员ですの
What the hell are you...
なんだお前は　ガキが大人しくひこんて
Kids should back off obedien—
なんだかなあ
How should I say thi—
被害者は近くの支部に任せて来ましたわ
I took the victims to the local branch.
御苦労さま
Good work.
いや　あんなストレンジを探して見つからなかったのに
We searched the Strange for so long,
普通に町でこいつらは捕まえられるんなんて
and now we easily find them in the city.
まあ　結果オーライですわ
Well, since we got good results, its all right.
All right then.
それもそっか
それじゃ
What's this?
なんだこりゃ
<judgement>
风纪委员ですの
We're Judgement.
What's with these brats?
なんだこいつら
ガキがふざけてんじゃねえぞ
Little kids shouldn't be messing with us.
Huh, Judgement?
ああ　风纪委员だ
What business do you have here?
いったい何の用だよ
黒妻綿流ですわね
You must be Kurozuma Wataru.
Huh?
能力者を対象とした暴行事件の首謀者として拘束します
You're under arrest for being the leader of these acts of violence against ability users.
Oh? Under arrest, huh?
拘束ねえ
悪いがおままごとに付き合ってる暇はねえだ
Sorry, but I don't have the time to play childish games with you guys.
帰りな
Leave.
言ってくれるわね
You shouldn't have said that.
I said it nicely, but if you don't understand it, then I'll explain it painfully.
親切で言ってやってんのに
分らねえなら体で分らせてやるよ
Onee-sama! I can handle these guys by myself.
御姉様　この程度の連中　私一人で十分での
十分かどうか　俺らの実力見てからにしろよな
Why don't you decide that after you've seen our real power for yourself!
What's this sound?
何　この音
頭に直接響くみたいですの
It's echoing directly in my head
どうした
What's wrong?
飛べない
I can't teleport!
どうした　お嬢ちゃん
What's wrong, Ojou-chan?
一人で十分じゃなかったのか
Evidently you can't handle us by yourself!
Kuroko!
黒子
What, no aim or power at all, it's as if—
そんな
狙いも威力も　まるで
Heh, can't control it, can you?
コントロールできなえか
Of course you wouldn't know, but this is a system called Capacity Down.
お前はもちろん知らないだろが
<capacity down>
こいつはキャパシティダウンってシステムだなあ
詳しいことが知らなえが
I don't know all the details, but it seems to
disrupt the mental processes of an ability user.
要するに音が脳の演算能力を混乱させるんだってよ
However, all we Skill-Outs hear is a high pitched sound.
<skill out>
ま　俺達武装無能力集団には
ただの甲高い音にしか聞こえねえけどな
How did they get something like this?!
こんな物一体どうやって
黒妻さん　許してくださいって言うなら
If you say "Please forgive us Kurozuma-san," I'll think about being nice again.
考えてやってもいいけどなあ
ええ　今は黒妻って言うのか
Eh? So now you call yourself Kurozuma?
It's him!
あいつだ
そうだ　あの男だ
That man!
黒妻さん　あの男です
Kurozuma-san, it's that guy! He's the one who's been getting our way!
俺達の邪魔を仕上がったのは
黒妻　さん
Kurozuma-san...
どういうことですの
What the heck is going on?
黒妻さん　どうしたんですか
Kurozuma-san! Kurozuma-san! What's wrong?!
Let's see here...
黒妻さん
音が　消えた
The sound!
It disappeared!
大丈夫か
Are you all right?
Huh?
そっちも
How about you?
あの
Um...
これ持ってるくれる
Could you hold this for me for a second?
蛇谷　久しぶりだな
Hebitani, it's been a long time.
嘘だ　あんた死んだはずだ
It can't be! You're supposed to be dead!
After all that, there's no way you could still be alive!
あれだけの事があって　生きてるはずがねえだ
じゃあ　幽霊ってことでいいや
Okay, does me being a ghost make it easier for you?
幽霊
A ghost?!
If you're a ghost, then I'll just send you back to your grave!
幽霊だったら
墓の下に戻せろう
ほら　やっちまえ
Get him! He's alone! We've got weapons!
相手は高が一人だ
こっちには武器があるんだろか
蛇谷　お前変わったな
Hebitani, you've changed.
死ねえ
Die!
止めとけ
You should stop.
お前らの腕じゃ 同士討ちせきにような
With you're skill level, you'll only cause friendly-fire.
Wait for us!
待ってくださいよ
どうだ　少しや楽になったか
How are you? Feeling better, now?
まだ力が入らない感じなんだけど 何とか
I still can't put much power through myself —
or something — but feeling somewhat better, yes.
あの男黒妻じゃないの
That man wasn't Kurozuma?
昔は蛇谷って言ったんだけどな
Back then he was called Hebitani.
今は黒妻って呼ばれてるらしい
However, it seems he calls himself Kurozuma now.
で　本物の黒妻は貴方ですのね
So, the real Kurozuma must be you, right?
そう呼ばれたこともあったかな
That was true a long time ago...
やっぱ牛乳は
Milk really has to be—
武蔵野牛乳
Musashino Milk.
固法先輩
Konori-sempai!
久しぶりだな　美偉
It's been a long time...
Mii.
Hmm?
Huh?
Eh?
A Certain Scientific Railgun
To be continued
What?!
狙い定めた指先が指す
運命は絶望 それとも希望
ゆらぎの中で受信してゆく
悲しみにも負けない
勇気だけをください
大切なもの　守るため
「強さ」があると信じてる
Saving our future 一緒に
明日へのドア明けいた空へ飛び立とう
とある世界の果てで
駆け抜けてくReal Force
光を放って
ねね　固法先輩どうしちゃったの
Hey, what's wrong with Konori-sempai?
Next Episode
学
园
都
市
Academy
City
何をあんなに悩んでるの
What is she all worried about?
ま　御姉様ったら
Oh no, my Onee-sama.
来週も大人なお話ですのよ
The next episode is for mature people again.